<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Amnesiac"><![CDATA[<b>Ability:</b> Remember who you were by selecting a graveyard role.
<br>
<br><b>Attributes:</b> When you choose a role it will be revealed to the town.
<br>
<br><b>Goal:</b> Remember who you were and complete that roles objectives. You can also survive at the end to win, like the Survivor.
<br>
<br><b>Note(s):</b>
<br><b>-</b>You may select a graveyard role who has been cleaned by the Janitor.
<br><b>-</b>You cannot select a graveyard role that is Unique. 
<br><b>-</b>If you get doused, then the arsonist dies and you remember you are an arsonist, you will die when you ignite yourself.
<br>
<br><b>Investigation Results:</b>
<br><u><i>Sheriff</i></u> - Not Suspicious
<br><u><i>Investigator</i></u> - Your target does not remember their role. They must be an Amnesiac.
<br><u><i>Consigliere</i></u> - Your target does not remember their role. They must be an Amnesiac.
<br>
<br><b>Win Conditions:</b>
<br>N/A]]></string>

    <string name="Survivor"><![CDATA[<b>Abilities:</b> Put on a bulletproof vest at night, protecting yourself from attacks.
<br>
<br><b>Attributes:</b>
<br><b>-</b>You can only use the bulletproof vest 4 times. (BUG: Sometimes, you cannot remove your vest once it has been worn).
<br><b>-</b>When you have a vest on, you cannot die (excluding the Arsonist\'s ignite, Jailor\'s execution, and Jester\'s haunt).
<br><b>-</b>Even if you are not attacked, your vest will get destroyed.
<br>
<br><b>Goal:</b> Live to the end of the game.
<br>
<br><b>Investigation Results:</b>
<br><u><i>Sheriff</i></u> - Not Suspicious
<br><u><i>Investigator</i></u> - Your target is a loner. They are either a Witch or Survivor.
<br><u><i>Consigliere</i></u> - Your target simply wants to live. They must be a Survivor.
<br>
<br><b>Win Conditions:</b>
<br>Win with Town
<br>Win with Serial Killers
<br>Win with Arsonists
<br>Win with Mafia
<br>Win with Witchs
<br>Win with Survivors]]></string>
</resources>
