<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Arsonist"><![CDATA[<b>Abilities:</b> Douse someone in gasoline or ignite all doused targets.
<br>
<br><b>Attributes:</b>
<br><b>-</b>Targets will know they are doused in gasoline.
<br><b>-</b>Death from fire can\'t be prevented by healing or night immunities.
<br><b>-</b>If you do not choose an action at night you will clean yourself.
<br>
<br><b>Goal:</b> Live to see everyone burn.
<br>
<br><b>Special Attributes:</b> Night Immunity, Ignores Night Immunity, Detection Immunity
<br>
<br><b>Note(s):</b>
<br><b>-</b>You will win a stalemate versus Godfather, Serial Killer and Jailor.
<br><b>-</b>A jailed target can be saved from being doused and ignited.
<br><b>-</b>You are able to ignite people that have been doused by other Arsonists.
<br>
<br><b>Investigation Results:</b>
<br><u><i>Sheriff</i></u> - Not Suspicious
<br><u><i>Investigator</i></u> - Your target smells like gas. They are either an Arsonist or a Transporter.
<br><u><i>Consigliere</i></u> - Your target enjoys watching things burn. They must be an Arsonist.
<br>
<br><b>Win Conditions:</b>
<br>Must kill Town
<br>Must kill Serial Killers
<br>Win kill Werewolves
<br>Must kill Mafia
<br>Win with Arsonists
<br>Win with Witches
<br>Win with Survivors]]></string>

    <string name="Serial_Killer"><![CDATA[<b>Abilities:</b> Kill someone each night.
<br>
<br><b>Attributes:</b> If you are role blocked you will attack the role blocker instead of your target. This includes the Escort, Consort, and Jailor.
<br>
<br><b>Goal:</b> Kill everyone who would oppose you.
<br>
<br><b>Special Attributes:</b> Night Immunity
<br>
<br><b>Note(s):</b>
<br><b>-</b>You will win with other Serial Killers.
<br><b>-</b>You will win a stalemate versus Godfather.
<br><b>-</b>You lose in a stalemate versus an Arsonist.
<br>
<br><b>Investigation Results:</b>
<br><u><i>Sheriff</i></u> - Your target is a Serial Killer.
<br><u><i>Investigator</i></u> - Your target is covered in blood. They must be a Doctor, Serial Killer, or Vampire.
<br><u><i>Consigliere</i></u> - Your target wants to kill everyone. They must be a Serial Killer.
<br>
<br><b>Win Conditions:</b>
<br>Must kill Town
<br>Must kill Arsonists
<br>Win kill Werewolves
<br>Must kill Mafia
<br>Win with Serial Killers
<br>Win with Witches
<br>Win with Survivors]]></string>

        <string name="Werewolf"><![CDATA[<b>Abilities:</b> Pillage a victim\'s home and anyone who visits them every Full Moon.
<br>
<br><b>Attributes:</b> If you are role blocked you will attack the role blocker instead of your target. This includes the Escort, Consort, and Jailor.
<br>
<br><b>Goal:</b> Kill everyone who would oppose you.
<br>
<br><b>Special Attributes:</b> Unique Role. Night Immunity when transformed. Ignores Night Immunity.
<br>
<br><b>Note(s):</b>
<br><b>-</b>Every Full Moon, you will transform into a Beast. You can choose to target a player\'s home, killing the occupant and anyone who visits, or you can choose to stay at home and kill anyone who visits your house.
<br><b>-</b>On a Full Moon, the Investigator will see you as a Werewolf.
<br><b>-</b>On a Full Moon, the Lookout will see you as \"beast\" if they choose to watch the house you pillage.
<br><b>-</b>Your pillage ignores Night Immunity.
<br><b>-</b>When jailed on a Full Moon, you will attack the Jailor if he chooses to not execute you.
<br><b>-</b>Both the Doctor and the Bodyguard can protect your target (or any of their visitors) from death. Only the Doctor\'s or Bodyguard\'s direct target will be saved.
<br>
<br><b>Investigation Results:</b>
<br><u><i>Sheriff</i></u> -
<br>Not Suspicious (on a regular night)
<br>Your target is a Werewolf (on a Full Moon)
<br><u><i>Investigator</i></u> - Your target is a loner. They must be a Werewolf, Witch, or Survivor.
<br><u><i>Consigliere</i></u> - Your target howls at the moon. They must be a Werewolf.
<br>
<br><b>Win Conditions:</b>
<br>Must kill Town
<br>Must kill Serial Killers
<br>Must kill Arsonists
<br>Must kill Mafia
<br>Win with Witches
<br>Win with Survivors]]></string>
</resources>
